  {
    "levelName": "Loops",
    "index": "3",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "0",
            "answer": "0"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "0"
          },
          {
            "problem": "2",
            "answer": "1"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "20",
            "answer": "190"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/OneStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/OneDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "-1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "0"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "57",
            "answer": "-1"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/TwoStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/TwoDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "0",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "3",
            "answer": "6"
          },
          {
            "problem": "4",
            "answer": "24"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "120"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/ThreeStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/ThreeDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "2, 10",
            "answer": "1024"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5, 5",
            "answer": "3125"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "1, 1",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5, 6",
            "answer": "15625"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/FourStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/FourDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "*\n"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "*****\n*****\n*****\n*****\n*****\n"
          },
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "******\n******\n******\n******\n******\n******\n"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "10",
            "answer": "**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/FiveStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/FiveDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  }